Guide to the David Petersen papers, [ca. 1989-1992].
Petersen, David papers, [ca. 1989-1992].
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
David Petersen papers, [ca. 1989-1992].
7626
David. Petersen
6 cubic ft.
Subject files, manuscripts, audiotapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files on early AIDS/insurance activism and ACT-UP files on health insurance; subject files pertaining to viatical settlements, financial planning, the New York State Health Care Reform bill, and the organizations New Yorkers for Affordable Health Care, and Affording Care.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Early member of Mariposa Foundation and later the head of Affording Care, a non-profit organization to help persons with AIDS get health insurance by cashing in life insurance policies.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files on early AIDS/insurance activism and ACT-UP files on health insurance; subject files pertaining to viatical settlements, financial planning, the New York State Health Care Reform bill. Also files regarding the organizations New Yorkers for Affordable Health Care, Mariposa, and Affording Care.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Petersen, David.; ACT-UP.; Affording Care.; Mariposa Foundation.; New Yorkers for Affordable Health Care.
Subjects:
Gays--Law and legislation.; AIDS activists.; AIDS (Disease)--Law and legislation.; Viatical settlements.; Insurance, Health--Law and legislation.; Insurance, Life--Law and legislation; New York State Health Care Reform Bill.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Where possible, original folder headings have been retained. The following are a list of common acronyms found in the guide:
BCBS: Blue Cross Blue Shield
EBCBS: Empire Blue Cross Blue Shield
GMHC: Gay Men's Health Center
HIAA: Health Insurance Association of America
PWAs: People With AIDS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Personal Materials
Box 1
Series II. Mariposa Files
Box 1
Series III. Insurance
Boxes 1-5
ACT-UP
Health Care Changes/Reforms
Government Benefits
Financial Planning
Miscellaneous Insurance Materials
Series IV. AIDS and General Health Files
Boxes 5-6
Series V. Miscellany
Box 6
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Personal Materials
  - Petersen resume, ca. 1970's (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Misc. personal materials, including invitations, mailings, etc. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series II. Mariposa Files
  - Misc. Mariposa mailings (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bequest appeal, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Financial committee, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mariposa stationary (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Info. re: forthcoming mailing, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mariposa project/budget, 1980? (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Structing FL? and planned giving, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Working file, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Financial statements, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mariposa DP? Solicitations, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Notebook contents, 3 ring, till 6/2/79" (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Series III. Insurance
  - ACT-UP
    - ACT-UP committee on insurance and access/Blue Cross/Blue Shield (BCBS), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - ACT-UP Insurance and access, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - ACT-UP IHAC, ERISA, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - NY Times Empire/Medicare, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - ACT-UP insurance, NATCA, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 20-24)
    - News articles from ACT-UP (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - ACT-UP Insurance Health Access Committee (AUIHAC)/Empire BCBS, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Health Care Changes/Reforms
    - BCBS Rate filing narrative summary, Feb. 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Cardone/BCBS correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - BCBS materials/correspondence re: NY Times article, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - "Empire Blue Cross Blue Shield" by David Petersen with Raymond Babin, for Body Positive magazine, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Testimonies re: BCBS rate increase request, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - BCBS rate increase materials, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - BCBS health care benefits materials, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - NY state health care changes (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - "Request of: EBCBS To: Department of Insurance of the State of NY for Approval of Community Rate Increases", 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Information on the rate-making process (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - EBCBS financial report, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - EBCBS misc., 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - RAND project memorandum: State Health Care Reform Initiatives, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Info. re: Wellstone Bill, including draft of bill and a press release by Sen. Wellstone, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - National health care reform information (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - National health care reform information from Aetna and BCBS, 1991? (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Medical care, at home care, national health care reform, etc. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - "The Status of State Regulation of Insurance Practices...", California, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Government Benefits
    - AIDS and financial services, financial help such as Medicaid (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Association Group Disability (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - COBRA (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
    - "Medicaid Eligibility for the Elderly in Need of Long Term Care", 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Disability insurance articles (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Disability information (Box 3, Folder 7-9)
    - GMHC info. on Supplemental Security Income, Medicaid, Medicare, etc. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - "Information on Availability of Medicare/Medicaid Manuals", by the USDHHS, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Medicaid teach-in materials, May 1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Medicare information (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - New York State Disability Insurance, 1989? (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Red Book on work incentives (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Social Security Disability and AIDS/HIV, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Social Security, Medicare, etc. misc. info. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - "Social Security and SSI Benefits for Children with Disabilities" brochure (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Veterans benefits (Box 3, Folder 19-20)
    - "White Paper on Fiduciary Purchases of Long-Term Care Insurance" and Medicare informational brochure (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Financial Planning
    - IAFP Convention: "Planning for Terminally Ill Clients", by David Petersen, 1989, tr7995a - tr7996a
    - "Financing Terminal Illness Through Viatical Settlements", by Life Management, the Lesbian & Gay Information Service, tr7997a
    - Bandfield, Richard (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Drugs by mail services (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Viatical settlements (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Intestacy (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Fenway Community Health Center (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Tuberculosis (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Disability Bookshop (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Second-to-Die Life Insurance (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Long term care insurance (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Viatical settlements articles (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Taxation of disability (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Planned giving (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Medicare supplements (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - HIV and nutrition (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - NY state Department of Health HIV Home Health Care Program Uninsured Fund (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Social Security (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Choice in dying (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Terminally ill (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Sex, AIDS, and Ethics (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - AIDS support organizations (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Infusion care/GMHC seminar series (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Health Insurance Association of America (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Divorce and financial planning (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Body Positive manual (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Gay & Lesbian Financial Planning Association (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Body Positive Seminar flyers, 3/28/1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Body Positive Seminar (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Insuring impaired risks (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - New Jersey Medical Insurance continuation (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Payroll & benefits administration companies- employee leasing (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - US Federation of Small Businesses, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Waiving co-insurance (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Stonewall Foundation (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - GHI open enrollment (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Estate planning (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Medical deductions- Income Tax (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - HIP (Health Insurance Plan) (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Leaving job, going on disability (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Estate planning information from Rothschild Law Offices (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - AIDS and financial planning (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - AIDS and finance background materials (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - "Financial Planning for the Terminally Ill", by the North Bay Chapter of the International Association for Financial Planning, May 1991 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Living Will and financial planning information (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Article re: living benefits and the terminally ill, by David Petersen (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Affording Care Bulletin, v.1 no.1, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Cost of AIDS (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Planners Bookstore Catalog, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - The Access Program (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - GMHC Legal Services Department debtor/creditor forum outline (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Petersen's notes on financial planning (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - "That Which Matters... A Financial Guide to Choices", by Peggy Wallace (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Insurance Materials
    - Misc. insurace reseach materials (Box 2)
    - 1990 Social Report of the Life and Health Insurance Business, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - ACLI/HIAA Survey of AIDS related claims, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - AHCPR (Agency for Health Care Policy and Research) reports (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - AIDS and the workplace, including information on health benefits (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "AIDS Costs and Utilization: Trends Among 10,438 Cases Insured by EBCBS", 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "AIDS, Health Insurance, and the Crisis of Community", draft(?), w/ edit notes (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - American Academy of Actuaries- "Risk Classification and AIDS", May 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - California and insurance issues (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - "Captive Insurance Companies" (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - "The Consumer's Guide to Health Insurance", printed by the HIAA (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Drafts of articles on insurance and HIV/AIDS, by David Petersen (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Focus employee benefits management booklets (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - "Funders Concerned About AIDS" information (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Health Care research and general health-related research miscellany (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Health Insurance misc. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Health insurance for gays (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - ICLU memo re: Westhoven n. Lincold Food Services Produce case (ERISA related), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Illinois comprehensive health insurance plan brochure (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Information for PWAs regarding insurance (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Info. from various health insurance providers on health plans (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - INS, IND services info (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Insurance industry AIDS initiative (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Insurance industry misc. (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - INS products- National Liberty (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Insurance issues (mainly NY state) (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Insurance related miscellany (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
    - Lasher Committee (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - The Lash Group: Health Care Consultants (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Legislative Report, information on health insurance and high risk pools, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Life insurance miscellany (Box 4, Folder 32-34)
    - Low-Load Life Insurance (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - "Medical Records: Getting Yours", by the Public Citizen Health Research Group, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Minimum Standards for Form, Content, and Sale of Health Insurance" (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Misc. HIV/AIDS and Insurance related materials (Box 4, Folder 38-42)
    - NAIC (National AIDS Information Services) Reference Search Resources Database (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - NAIC misc. (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - New York Study Manual for Life and Accident and Health Insurance (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - NY State Department of Health AIDS Institute Fair Share packet, Oct. 1991 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Oregon Health Plan, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Position Paper: Access to Health Care (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - "The Practice and Ethics of Risk- Rated Health Insurance", 1992 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - "The Role of Market Forces in the Delivery of Health Care", Apr. 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Russell Miller, Inc. insurance materials (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Search for product (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Society of Insurance Accountants (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Statement of the Health Insurance Association of America on Access to Health Care", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Statements/testimonies re: Small Business Health Insurance (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "Taking the Bite Out of Insurance", by James Hunt (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Texas info. on HIV medication programs, food stamps, social security, etc. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - The Bulletin: AIDS Special Report, Mar. 1909 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Title II Insurance: "Open Enrollment Requirements..." (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - United Chambers Insured Plans: Group Insurance Certificate Booklet (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - US Healthcare- NY State Plans (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Wellcare of New York (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Where to get Health Insurance (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Insurance-related news clippings and articles (Box 5, Folder 15-21)
- Series IV. AIDS and General Health Files
  - 8th International Conference on AIDS/3rd STD World Congress Summary Report, July 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - AAPHR (American Association of Physicians for Human Rights) 11th Annual Symposium Packet, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - AIDS/HIV resources for Greater Houston (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - "AIDS in Semi-Rural Northern California", 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - AIDS in the workplace (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - AIDS Medical Foundation News Release, June 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - AIDS related clippings, newsletters, etc. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - AIDS resources, influding "Where to get AIDS/HIV information in NYC" booklet (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - AIDS treatment information and other medical issues regarding AIDS (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - "A New Life" by A. Buonarabo (a poem) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Bronx AIDS Forum (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - CDC (Center for Disease Control) and AIDS (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - CDC Natoinal AIDS Clearinghouse Network Contact Support Guide, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Citizens Commission on AIDS for NYC and Northern NJ packet (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence from D. Petersen to KNME-TV re: info. on PWAs, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Clippings (Box 5, Folder 37-39)
  - Dying and Death (thenatology) materials (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Flyer for free AIDS drugs (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Gay health (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Gay and lesbian health fair (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - GMHC related materials (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - "Helping People Cope: A Guide for Families Facing Cancer", 1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Home care devices (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Informational articles/packets on AIDS and AIDS treatment (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - "The Male Prostitute, AIDS, and Public Policy..." by Michael L. Feiersten (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Product release flow chart (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Manhattan Plaza AIDS Project Information Packet (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan Plaza AIDS Project materials (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Manhattan Plaza AIDS Project- volunteer name and address list, Sept. 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Marke Lowe Fisher, including clippings about protests after his death, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Medical research (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Misc. AIDS materials- political, personal support related (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Misc. HIV/AIDS related flyers, brochures, information, etc. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - National Association of People With AIDS (NAPWA) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Network Contact Support Guide", by the CDC, OCt. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - New HIV/AIDS treatments (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - New York Physicians for Human Rights (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - The NYC AIDS Fund, 1990 Grant Recipients (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - "Positive Survival with AIDS: A Clinical Study of Longterm Survivors", 1992? (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - "Protease Inhibitors: Current and Future Use", Jan. 1996 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Survival trends in AIDS (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Scientific American issues on AIDS, 10/1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - US General Accounting Office Health Reports, Nov. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Series V. Miscellany
  - Anita Bryant Ministries public opinion survey (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Avanti market research (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Berkowitz + Callen articles (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - BWMT (Black and White Men Together) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Condom Card (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - CURE (Congress United for Rights & Equality) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Drafts of letters re: the Internal Revenue Code (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Entertainment (club flyers, etc.) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Flyers/mailings from misc. GLBT organizations (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Gay and Michigan, incl. "Sexual Orientation Report and REcommendations" as adopted by the Michigan CRC, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Gay background (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Gay market (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Gay Market Report and related materials, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Gay money (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Gay-related news clippings (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
  - "Gay Teachers: A Disesteemed Minority in an Overly Esteemed Profession", by Joshua Dressler (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Gay trust (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - GGBC (Greater Gotham Business Council) materials (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Info. from the Small Business Service Bureau (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Lesbian and Gay Law Students of NYU Law School press release, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Market research questionnairre (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Minutes of the Task Force for the Hearings of the NYC HRC on the quality of life of NY gay citizens, Sept. 19, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Misc. pamphlets/brochures (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - National Association of Social Workers (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - National Register of Lesbian and Gay Unions (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - NGTF related materials, including call for co-Executive Director applicaitons (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - OutLoud: The Lesbian and Gay Cultural & Business Expo, Feb. 1994 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Pert Chart (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Paper: "Sexual Identity and Self Concept", by Paul C. Larson, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - RentSmart: A Consumer Guide to Residential Leases (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - SAGE (Senior Action in a Gay Environment) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Statement from Craig Rodwell re: Segal sculpture in Christopher Park, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - The Wall Stree Project, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - "Twinkie Power" bumper sticker (Box 6, Folder 53)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The following periodicals have been seperated from the collection and cataloged individually:
AIDS Clinical Care, v.3 no.7
AIDS Forum, v.1 no.1
AIDS Patient Care, v.2 no.5
AIDS Treatment News, #159,160
AIDS Update (Dallas, TX), v.8 no.9
BETA, 1994:Dec., 1995: Dec.
The Blade (Washington DC), 1979: Oct. 25
Bulletin of the Philadelphia Lesbian and Gay Task Force, v.2:no.3,5
The Bulleting (Mercer Meidinger Hansen), no.156,159
Center Happenings, 1990:Jan/Feb
The Center Voice., v.6 no.2,6
Center Stage, 1989:Sept./Oct. 1990:Jan.
Cleis Press, Spring 1985 Catalog
Columbus Free Press, v.8 no.12
Community Prescription Service InfoPack, v.4 no.2
The Connection (LI, NY, NJ), v.2 no.14
CRIA Update, 1992: Spring, Summer
Critical Path AIDS Project, v.3 no.6-8
DIFFA On Line, v.1 no.3
Diseased Pariah News, #2
Gay Roots, the Elysian Fields Booklist, no.101-102
GMAD (Gay men of African Descent), 1989: Sept./Oct.
Elysian Fields recent acquisitions catalog, #18
Friends Newsletter, 1992:Fall
Gay Ohio Living Data, issue 2
The Gay Traveller.
Gays on the Hill, v.2:no.2, v.3:no.1
GGBC Newsletter, 1980: June, July 1981:Feb.
GLAAD Bulletin, 1989: Oct/Nov
GLAAD Newsletter, 1989: Fall
GMHC Annual Report, 1989/199
GMHC: The Volunteer, v.7: no.5-6, v.8 no.6, v.9:no.4
Good Times Bookshop, Catalog #1
Gotham, v.2:no.4,8-9,12,16
Hemophilia Outlook, 1993: Winter
High Gear. V.6 no.5
HIV Advisor, v.7 no.2
HIV Education Case Studies, no.4
HIV Frontline, #12
HIV Notebook, 1992:Oct/Nov/Dec, 1993:Winter
Homosexuelle Emanzipation. 1979:Mai/Juni,Juli/Aug.
It's Time. V.5:no.10, v.6:no.2, v.7:no.3,4,6
Living HIV, v.1 no.1
MACT/NY v.11: no.6
Michael's Thing Weekly, v.17:no.38
MOHR, v.3 no.9
Mothers' Voices, v.3 no.2
NAPWA News, v.3 no.4
National Minority AIDS Council Update, 1992: Sept./Oct.
News From Lambda, 1980: summer
The New Voice, issue546.
New York City News. v.1:no.4, v.2:no.4
NGTF Action Report, 1978:Dec., 1979:Feb.
Notes from the Underground, no.1,19-20,22-23,25-26,30-31
Ohio Gay Rights Coalition Newsletter, v.3 no.3
Oscar Wilde Memorial Bookshop Catalog, Spring 1979
Outfront, v.2 no.1
Outweek, no.42
Positively Aware, 1994:May
Provincetown Directory, 1982
Provincetown Positive, no.12
PWA Coalition Newsline, #57
Spartacus: Good News Letter, no.9
TA: Technical Assistance Newsletter, 1992: Aug/Sept
Walt Whitman Bookshop, Catalog no.2, v.1-2.
The Weekly News, v.3 no.21